# SEBASTIAN CURTIS LAVARIAS

**WEB DEVELOPER** 

Mobile: 09972217704

E-mail: sebastiancurtislavarias@gmail.com

Web: https://bastilavarias.github.io Github: https://github.com/bastilavarias

Home Address:

406 Sta Fe St. Tondo Manila, Philippines

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm Sebastian Curtis Lavarias, 21 years old. I believe that great things can be done by a group of people through unity, trust, and teamwork. I make sure to follow through and finish the commitments that I have and I can adapt easily to different kinds of situations.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Vue.js / Sass
- PHP / Laravel / Node.js
- SOL
- Amazon Web Services
- Git

## **EDUCATION**

**Universidad De Manila**BS Information Technology

2018 - Present

Metropolitan Medical Center College of Arts Science & Technology

Senior Highschool 2016 - 2018

**Tondo High School** 

Highschool 2012 - 2016

Magat Salamat Elementary School

Elementary 2006 - 2012

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Freelance Web Developer

Dec 2021 - Present Part-time

#### **Notable Clients:**

#### Malabon LGU

- Used Vue, Laravel, MySQL, and AWS Technologies.
- Developed, implemented features, and made revisions to Malabon City Hall HRIS, Malabon Barangay System, and City of Malabon University Portal.

#### Vaskeappen

- Used Vue, Google Cloud Platform, and AWS Technologies.
- Developed the admin portal of the Vaskeappen App.

## Web Developer

Fourello | Dec 2020 - Dec 2021 Full-time

- Used Vue, Laravel, Node, and AWS Technologies.
- Converted UI/UX designs to an interactive website.
- Developed responsive and mobile-friendly web applications.
- Implemented and made APIs according to the business requirements.
- Led a team consisting of developers to implement features to a project.